原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
今晚谁有空
Hey, uh, who's free tonight?
-我应该有...  -别急
- Oh, I think I'm... - Hang on.
我们犯过这个错误
We've made this mistake before.
害自己身陷他亲戚迪帕克的特百惠直销派对
It's how we wound up at his cousin Deepak's Tupperware party.
当时会上买的折叠碗你少用了吗
Hey, you use that collapsible bowl all the time,
你自己心里清楚
and you know it.
而且这次不是那样
And it's not like that.
我只是想我们可以聚一起  去酒吧什么的
I just thought we could, you know, hang out and go to a bar.
-行吧  -感觉可以
- Sure. - ??Sounds fun.
然后看板球比赛
And watch cricket.
板球是印度最流行的运动之一
现在听到的声音  很讽刺的也是蟋蟀[板球]
That sound you hear, ironically, crickets.
大伙们
Hey, guys.
伯特  你好吗
Hey, Bert, how you doing?
你懂的
Well, you know,
每当"石"月过了  我们地质学家都会有点伤心
we geologists always get a little sad when Rocktober's over.
-文字哏吗  -对
- Wordplay?  - Yes.
好笑的文字哏吗
Funny wordplay?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
相信你的直觉
Trust your gut.
谢尔顿  我有一些40亿年前的陨石
Sheldon, I've got these four-billion-year-old meteorites.
我觉得或许能找到中微子交互作用的痕迹
I thought maybe they'd show signs of neutrino interactions.
我真的很需要你这样的人才
I could really use someone like you
来帮忙计算部分
to help me with the math.
所以它们能当做是天然的暗物质探测器
Oh, so they would act as natural dark matter detectors.
感觉很有意思
That sounds interesting.
是啊  但始终还是地质学
It does, but it's still geology.
抱歉了  伯特  我没空跟你玩石头
Sorry, Bert, I don't have time to play rocks with you.
我不是找你来玩石头
I'm not asking you to play rocks.
是来找你合作研究项目
I'm asking you to collaborate on a research project.
不过如果有时间
Although, if there's time,
我们可以玩挖矿桌游"矿藏"
I guess we could play a round of zinc, zinc, piece of quartz.
感觉比看板球有意思多了
Does sound better than cricket.
谢谢你的邀请
Thank you for asking.
但很抱歉  我有真正的科学工作要做
Unfortunately, I have real science to do.
祝你石石快乐  石来运转
But you feel free to rock on.
这才叫玩转文字哏
That's how you do it.
好吧
All right.
谢尔顿  你这是干嘛呢
Sheldon, what are you doing?
伯特好歹也是他领域的顶尖人物
Bert's one of the top guys in his field.
世上某处也有个哑剧界一霸呢
And somewhere there's a mime who's top in his field,
你有看到我冲过去跟他合作演出
but you don't see me rushing to collaborate with him
新版的被困在空气盒子里表演吗
on new ways to be stuck in a box.
又一个比板球更吸引我的东西
Also something I would watch instead of cricket.
你好啊
Hello.
谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon.
我心里琢磨了一阵子
I've been thinking about it,
我想我可以来帮忙你的研究
and I suppose I-I could help you with your research.
是什么让你改变了心意
What changed your mind?
伯特  当人家送你马
Bert, I'm a gift horse.
检查马牙口是很不礼貌的
Don't look me in the mouth.
是我不好  我很高兴你愿意帮忙
Sorry. I'm happy you want to help out.
如果这里不方便  我们可以去你办公室
If it's easier for you, we could just work at your office.
不不不  不去我办公室
No, no, no, not my office, no.
就在这里吧
Uh, let's-let's do it here,
等晚上大家都回家后再开工
in-in the evenings, after everyone's gone home.
那我得看看我晚上有没有空
I just have to see if my evenings are free.
那是玩笑话  我有空
That's a joke. They are.
好的  那我们今晚见
Okay. Well, then I will see you tonight.
其实呢
Well, you know what?
关上百叶窗  我们现在就能开工
Close the blinds. We can start right now.
翻译     驭女学家赛太公  油腻希  猫中之王
校对     针扎心里赛太公   纸扎身体YY猫
后期      灰灰是菇凉      时间轴    加森
总监     新浪微博@赛太公
生
活
大
爆
炸
第十一季  第七集
我真不懂板球哪里有趣了
I don't get how you can enjoy cricket.
毫无逻辑可言
It makes no sense.
你来就是为了唧唧歪歪吗
Did you just come here to complain?
对啊  那是我们犹太人热衷的运动
Yeah. That's the sport of my people.
那个人是罗微查得兰·阿湿文  他超厉害
Ooh, that's Ravichandran Ashwin. He's amazing.
能让哈迪克·庞德亚感觉像波文尼什瓦·库玛一样菜
He makes Hardik Pandya look like Bhuvneshwar Kumar.
喂喂喂  给我们其他人取名时留点字用吧
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, save some syllables for the rest of us.
那边那个好像是伯纳黛特的朋友
Hey, I think that's Bernadette's friend over there.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
如琪
Hey, Ruchi!
希望不会太尴尬
I-I hope this isn't awkward.
上次我跟她见面  我有点丢人
The last time we met, I kind of embarrassed myself.
看看你这次能不能再接再丢人
Let's see if you can go two for two.
-你们好啊  -你来啦
- Hey, guys. - ?Hey.
你自己一个人来吗
Hi. ?Are you here by yourself?
对啊  我说服不了任何人来陪我看
Yeah, I couldn't convince anyone to come watch cricket with me.
可不是嘛  我也是硬拉他来的
Tell me about it. I had to drag this guy.
欢迎你加入我们一起看啊
You're more than welcome to join us if you'd like.
谢谢啊
Thanks.
阿力乌丝科当配波卡
Arre uske taang pay ball kar!
她说什么
What'd she say?
乌丝科当配波卡
Uske taang pay ball kar.
你一说我就"懂"了
Oh, that clears that up.
不是啦  她是在叫投球手投脚前球
Well, no, she's telling the bowler to bowl a yorker.
是板球里最凶的一种球
It's the most brutal ball in cricket.
我去了巴基斯坦球星肖波连投俩脚前球的比赛
I was at the match when Shoaib bowled back-to-back yorkers.
我也去了呢  真是缘分啊
Well, I was there, too! What a coincidence!
当时有12万人去看了比赛  所以...
Well, there were 120,000 people at that match, so...
印度嘛  对吧  无论去哪里
Yeah, India, right? Everywhere you go,
都有大概12万人左右
there's, like, 120,000 people.
你觉得我们板球世界杯赢的几率如何
So what do you think of our chances at the World Cup?
世界杯吗
Ah, World Cup.
全看科利的打击手感好不好了
You know, it'll all depend if Kohli's batting in form.
对啊  无论你队伍里多少全能手都没用
I know. It doesn't even matter how many all-rounders you have.
可不是嘛
Isn't that the truth?
你知道我是我高中最厉害的旋球投手吗
You know, I was the best leg spinner in my high school?
我投的曲线球最刁钻了
Yeah, like, I bowled the meanest googly.
说到曲线球...  我要曲线走人了
Speaking of googlies, I'm gonna go.
我给不同种的暗物质
I've been modeling different types of dark matter
以及它们会在你的陨石里的
and the traces they would leave
锆石留下的痕迹都建了模
on the zircon inside your meteorite.
这个是什么
What's this one here?
是我个人独创的暗物质模型
That's actually a dark matter model of my own creation.
我取名为库珀玻色子
I call it the Cooper boson.
厉害  我也曾有机会给石头命名
Cool. I got to name a rock once.
我取名为中等沉积页岩
I named it Moderately Sedimented Shale.
那个名字我可能取得挺屎
Guess I kind of pooped the bed on that one.
伯特  我不得不说
You know, Bert, I've got to say,
这研究出乎意料地让我乐在其中
this work has been surprisingly engaging.
对啊  其实挺酷的
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
艾米
Hello, Amy.
什么叫我在哪里
What do you mean, where am I?
我在我办公室啊
I'm in my office.
才没有  我在你办公室外  你不在
No, I'm at your office and you're not here.
我本来想给你惊喜  带了晚饭来
I thought I'd surprise you with dinner.
以后请记得  最好的惊喜
For future reference, the best surprises
是我提前三天就先知情的那种
are the ones I know about three days in advance.
你到底在哪
Where are you?
也是个惊喜  感觉不好受  是吧
It's a surprise. Doesn't feel so good, does it?
我有吃的
Well, I have food.
我本来是想找你一起吃
I thought we could eat together,
但如果你有其他的安排...
but I guess if you have other plans...
什么  我在这里啊
What?! I'm here!
就在我跟你说的地点
Exactly where I said I was.
开吃吧
Let's eat.
你们好啊
Hello.
你来啦  怎么了
Hey, buddy, what's up?
我需要跟佩妮单独聊聊
Um, I need to talk to Penny alone.
有何能为您效劳
What can I do for you?
稍等一下  我得确定莱纳德听不到
Just a minute, I want to make sure Leonard can't hear us.
我带了一盒小蛋糕
I've got a box of cupcakes.
没问题了
Okay, we're good.
我跟伯特合作了  但我不想别人知道
I'm working with Bert, but I don't want anyone to find out.
你已经泄露给我了  好的开始啊
Well, you just told me, so strong start.
佩妮  事关重大
Penny, this is serious.
我的名誉悬于一线
My reputation is on the line.
其他人看到我们合作会怎么想啊
What are people gonna think when they see us collaborating?
不知道呢  觉得伯特很可怜吧
I don't know. Poor Bert?
我是一名德高望重的理论物理学家
I am a respected theoretical physicist.
我立志有一天得到诺贝尔奖
I aspire to win a Nobel Prize someday.
但要是其他人发现我涉足地质学
But nobody's gonna take me seriously
就不会把我当回事了
if they find out I've been dabbling in geology.
为什么  这两种都是科学啊
Well, why not? They're both sciences.
而我会知道是因为
And I know because they're classes
我高中的辅导员说这两门课"不适合我"
my high school counselor said "weren't for me."
这两者差别极大
They're very different.
物理学解答了
Physics answers the question:
宇宙的本质是什么
what is the nature of the universe?
地质学解答了  我刚才是被什么绊倒了
Geology answers the question: what'd I just trip over?
好吧  那就别跟伯特合作呗
All right, well, then don't work with Bert.
-但我喜欢那研究  -那就跟他合作
- Oh, but I like the work. - Then work with him.
可我觉得那个领域很丢人
Yeah, but I'm ashamed of the field.
-那别合作了  -但我们也许能证明暗物质
- Then don't work with him. - Yeah, but we could prove dark matter.
-那就合作吧  -但我觉得其他人...
- Then work with him. - But I just think that people...
我们还得这样来回纠结多少回
How many times are you gonna do this?
我的记录是14回
My record is 14.
这是跟科学有关的事
Okay, this is about science.
你为什么来问我
Why'd you come to me?
因为这也跟我的名誉有关
Well, because it's also about my reputation.
而你尽管有着错综复杂的过去
And somehow you manage to hold your head high
但现在还依然能保有谜之自信
despite your checkered past.
错综复杂的过去
Checkered past?
这是个比喻
It's a figure of speech
形容你以前作风不检点
referring to how sexually promiscuous you were.
真的吗
Really?
我也有句比喻
Well, I've got a figure of speech about
你可以"去你的"房间跟自己不检点
how sexually promiscuous you can go be with yourself.
什么话
And what is it?
在伯纳黛特卧床休息期间
Look, while Bernadette's on bed rest,
我们必须分而治之
we're gonna have to divide and conquer.
这两个监视器一个监视她  一个监视宝宝
I've got one monitor for her, one for the baby.
你想要哪个
Which do you want?
我选宝宝的吧  她没那么欺负人
I'll take the baby. She's less emasculating.
早上好
Good morning!
-吃司康饼吗  -好啊  谢谢
- Scones? - ?Ah, thanks.
这是买给你们的  我已经在如琪家吃过早餐了
They're all for you; I already had breakfast at Ruchi's.
不会吧  你跟她睡了吗
You're kidding. You slept with her?
倒是没有多少时间在睡觉啦
Well, there wasn't a lot of sleeping involved.
我意思是她睡了  我醒着
I mean, she slept, I stayed awake.
我怕打呼  因为我没带我的特殊防打鼾枕
I was afraid of snoring 'cause I didn't have my special pillow.
霍华德
Howard!
过来扶我去洗手间
Can you help me to the bathroom?!
至少我们之间浪漫还没死绝
Well, at least the romance is still alive.
你和如琪啊
So, you and Ruchi?
对  抱歉  我知道你也喜欢她
Yeah, I'm sorry. I know you liked her, too,
但我们昨晚碰到了  聊出了火花
but we just bumped into each other last night and hit it off.
不  没关系
No, that's fine.
你是我的朋友  我为你高兴
You're my friend and I'm happy for you.
谢谢你  斯图尔特
Oh, thank you, Stuart.
再说了  虽然我还不知道你会怎么搞砸
Plus, I don't know how you're gonna screw it up,
但我知道你迟早会搞砸
but I know you will.
有什么好搞砸的
What's there to screw up?
她也只是想随意一点交往
She just wants to keep things casual.
太好了  这就是你会搞砸的原因
Oh, great, that's how you're gonna screw it up.
我也可以很随意啊
Hey, I can be casual.
我得赶紧去理个发  这段关系很快就会玩完
I should get a haircut; this thing's going south fast.
我和如琪决定让感情随意发展
So Ruchi and I decided to keep things casual.
怎么了
What? What?
我也可以只动鸡不动心
I can handle casual.
你为什么一直做出那个嘴
Why do you keep doing that with your face?
因为你嘴里一直吐出蠢话
Because you keep saying stupid things with yours.
好吧
Okay, fine.
我的确不擅长随意的恋爱关系
I'm not great at casual relationships,
但我不想把她吓跑
and I don't want to scare her off.
给她一点空间就行了
All right, just give her some space, all right?
别打电话  别发短信  别发邮件
Don't call, don't text, don't e-mail.
那怎么行
That's crazy.
要是我看到夕阳想起她时怎么办
What if I see a sunset that reminds me of her?
你们下一次见面是什么时候
All right, when do you see her next?
我们今晚一起吃晚餐
Uh, we're having dinner tonight.
好  在手腕上绑一根皮筋
Okay, put a rubber band around your wrist,
每次你开始策划你们的婚礼
and any time you start planning your wedding
或是给你们的孩子取名时
or naming your children,
你就用叉子扎自己的手
I want you to stab yourself in the hand with a fork.
那皮筋是用来干嘛的
What's the rubber band for?
用来减缓失血
To slow the bleeding.
伯纳黛特卧床休息得怎么样了
Hey, how's Bernadette handling bed rest?
她整天都躺在床上
She lies around all day
吃吃巧克力  对我大声嚷嚷
eating Mallomars and hollering at me,
她从我老婆转变为我妈的过程已经完成了
so her transformation from my wife to my mother is complete.
恭喜  我知道你就盼着这一天
Congratulations. I know that's what you were hoping for.
谢尔顿  你昨晚把外套落在我办公室了
Sheldon, you left your jacket in my office last night.
我没有  我才没有
Uh, oh. No-no, I didn't.
那外套都不是我的
That's-that's not my jacket.
那上面怎么写着
Then why does it say,
"谢·库珀所有物  别碰"
"Property of S. Cooper. Stop touching it"?
听起来某个叫谢库珀的人
It sounds like someone named Scooper
不希望你碰他的外套
doesn't want you touching his jacket.
你们是在合作研究那个陨石项目吗
Are you guys working together on that meteorite project?
是的  好吧  被你们发现了
Yes, fine, you found me out.
我现在玩地质学了
I'm doing geology.
拜托千万别说出去
Just, please, don't tell anyone.
你觉得我很丢人吗
Are you embarrassed of me?
不不不  不是你
Oh, no, no, no, not you.
只是你毕生所投身于的研究事业丢人
No, just the work that you've devoted your entire life to.
如果你觉得和我合作很丢人
If you're ashamed to be working with me,
那我也不想和你合作
then I don't want to work with you.
谢尔顿  刚才真的很过分
Sheldon, that was pretty rude.
他过分不很正常吗  毕竟是个地质学家
Well, what do you expect? He's a geologist.
这地方挺高级的
This place seems nice.
也不算很高级
Uh, but not too nice.
点评网说这儿"适合聚会"
Yelp called it "Good for groups."
你想为这位女士买...
Would you care to buy the lady a...?
不要  走开
No! Get out of here!
抱歉
Sorry about that.
我很讨厌有人擅自认为别人在交往
I just, I hate when someone assumes two people are dating
就因为他们看起来
just because they look like
能制造出可爱美丽的宝宝
they would make beautiful babies together.
你确定你能接受这样的关系吗
Are you sure you're okay with this?
老实说  如琪  我在随意的男女关系这方面
Honestly, Ruchi, I don't have a lot of experience
经验不多
with casual relationships.
我在认真的男女关系方面略有经验
I have some experience with serious relationships
在没有男女关系方面经验超多
and a ton of experience with no relationships.
你真幽默
You're funny.
很庆幸你能这么解读
Glad it came off that way.
说说你今天过得怎么样
Uh, so tell me about your day.
工作进行得如何
How's work going?
我一早上都在研究那款真菌乳膏的副作用
Well, I spent the morning reviewing side effects for our fungal cream,
看了很多流脓和分泌物
so it was a lot of ooze and pus.
♪ 宛如天堂 ♪
♪ Almost paradise ♪
Almost paradise - Mike Reno/Ann Wilson
♪ 天堂之门我们触手可及 ♪
♪ We are knocking on heaven's door ♪
♪ 宛如天堂 ♪
♪ Almost paradise ♪
然后我得把它们归类
And then I had to catalog it
按照颜色  黏度
by color, viscosity
以及血液百分比
and percentage of blood.
听起来很美妙
Sounds wonderful.
那是什么
What you got there?
一块石头
A rock.
是某个恶毒的小男孩砸你的吗
Did some mean boys throw it at you?
事实证明我才是那个恶毒的小男孩
It turns out I'm the mean boy.
不过我的确有砸到自己的脚  所以你没说错
Although I did drop it on my own foot, so kind of.
出什么事了
What's going on?
如果我想做一件事
What if there was something I wanted to do,
但又怕别人会看不起我  怎么办
but I was worried other people would think less of me?
如果别人是指我  而你想做的是卧室中的事
Is that other person me, and does it happen in the bedroom,
那我觉得放马过来
in which case I think I'm cool with it?
不是
No.
我是指和伯特一起...
It's about working with Bert on...
算了  我都说不出口
You know what? I'm not even gonna say it.
我就小小地透露一下这个词的第一个字
I am just gonna say the letter it starts with
和最后一个字"学"
and "Ology."
"地"  哎呀  我都剧透完了
"G"-- Oh, no, that's not gonna work.
地质学吗
Geology?
没错  但我们散伙了
Yes. But we parted ways
因为我担心自己的名誉受损
because I was worried about my reputation.
谢尔顿  你从来都没在意过别人的看法
Sheldon, you've never cared what people thought,
即使在你真的应该在意的时候
even when you really, really should.
比如上次和我父母吃饭的时候
That dinner with my parents comes to mind.
如果和你妈见面时
If I'm not gonna use "Your momma" jokes
不能开"你老母"的玩笑  那我去学了干嘛
when I meet your mother, why'd I bother to learn them?
我只是想说  如果你觉得项目有趣
I'm just saying, if you think the work is interesting,
那就不需要考虑其他的事情
nothing else should matter.
你说得对  艾米
You're right, Amy.
这真是金玉良言
That is sage advice.
真是神奇  毕竟你老母那么笨...
Which is surprising, considering your momma is so dumb, she...
滚
Nope.
笨到尿液"测验"都得读书
She studied for a urine test.
我本来应该回印度结婚的
I was supposed to go back to India and get married,
但我意识到这不是我想要的
but I realized it wasn't what I wanted.
所以我取消了订婚  搬到了这里
So I called off the engagement and moved out here.
如果他不是你的灵魂伴侣  那他就不是对的人
Well, if he wasn't your soul mate, he wasn't your soul mate.
天啊  拜托你千万不要是那种人
Oh, God, please tell me you're not one of those.
哪种人
One of whats?
我想说少女心的小女孩  但好像太毒了
I want to say teenage girls, but that sounds mean.
你不相信每个人都有命中注定的另一半吗
Come on, you don't believe that everyone has one perfect match?
当然不信了  太荒唐了
Of course not. That's ridiculous.
万一你的灵魂伴侣住在地球的另一半呢
I mean, what if your soul mate lived halfway across the world?
那你就永远见不到了
You'd never meet.
你当然能见到
Yes, you would.
我可以给你随便举20个例子
I can give you, like, 20 examples
那还只是发生在凯特·哈德森一个人身上的
where that happened to Kate Hudson alone.
美国女演员  浪漫爱情喜剧专业户
算了吧
You know what?
每次我说起这个  都会惹别人不高兴
People get upset when I talk about this.
我们还是换个话题吧
Let's just change the subject.
不不不  没关系
No, no, no. No, it's-it's fine.
所以你不相信两个人会真心相爱吗
Are you saying that you don't believe two people fall in love?
他们当然会啊
Of course they do.
只不过人们所谓的"爱"
It's just that what people call "Love"
其实是大脑中的一系列化学反应作祟
is actually a series of biochemical reactions
会随着时间流逝而消逝
in the brain that fade over time.
没错  就像那首老歌唱的
Yes. Like the old song,
迈克尔·波顿名曲《当男人爱上女人》
"当男人化学反应上女人"
"When a man has a biochemical reaction for a woman."
拉杰  我们都是科学家
Raj, we're scientists.
就算我们了解恋爱产生的机制
We don't need to feel threatened just because we understand
我们也不需要觉得害怕
the mechanisms that give rise to romantic feelings.
这对恋爱的体验没有任何的影响
It doesn't take anything away from the experience.
当然有影响了
Yes, it does.
老实说  这完全毁掉了恋爱的感觉
Actually, it takes everything away from it.
爱情不仅仅是科学
Love isn't just science.
它更是精神上的
Okay? It's-it's spiritual.
那是一种令人捉摸不定的
It's an acknowledgment of a mystery
神秘体验
that's greater than ourselves.
是爱让人们吟诗颂曲
It's what makes people write songs and poems,
让《黄金单身汉》真人秀精彩了21季
and what has kept The Bachelor on TV for 21 magical seasons.
你不认为在游戏节目中把爱作为奖品送出去
Don't you think the fact that love is given away as a prize
正好削弱了你的观点吗
on a game show slightly undermines your argument?
没错
Uh, yes.
但我一集都没落下
But I've never missed an episode,
你能用科学解释这件事吗
and I dare science to explain that.
伯特
Bert.
伯特  伯特
Bert, Bert.
伯特  伯特  伯特
Bert, Bert, Bert.
你想干嘛  谢尔顿
What do you want, Sheldon?
我希望咱们能重新一起工作
I would like us to work together again.
我保证不再乱发表地质学的言论
I promise to keep my geology comments to myself,
因为这些言论都太过分了  虽然有些很好笑
because while some of them are funny, all of them are mean.
这下尴尬了
Well, this is awkward.
莱纳德  你在这里干什么
Leonard, what are you doing here?
伯特找了我帮忙
Bert asked for my help.
他是一个优秀的科学家
Yeah, he's an excellent scientist,
也不规定我上厕所的时间
and he doesn't tell me what time I can go to the bathroom.
我那是膀胱训练
It's called bladder training.
等你到了80岁  你会感谢我的
When you're in your 80s, you'll thank me for it.
听着  谢尔顿  你对伯特不好
Look, Sheldon, you were a jerk to Bert,
所以他不和你玩了
and he walked away from you.
我觉得我可以向他好好讨教一番
So I feel like there's a lot he could teach me.
伯特  拜托
Bert, please.
我知道自己之前表现不太好
I know I behaved poorly in the past,
但这次我保证会有所改变
but things will be different this time.
你会看到的
You'll see.
拜托  让我进来吧
Come on, let me in.
我们会一起欢笑
We'll have some laughs,
一起计算同位素比值
we'll calculate some isotope ratios.
抱歉  谢尔顿
I'm sorry, Sheldon.
你就这样让他吃闭门羹吗
So you just shut the door in his face?
我得开始记录下你的招数了
I got to start writing this stuff down.
虽然如琪是个好人
I mean, Ruchi's nice.
但我俩太不同了
We're just so different.
我懂你  有时候跟别人交往
I know. Sometimes when you're dating,
都会碰到奇奇怪怪的人
you meet weird people.
我还交往过不喜欢看人杂耍的女孩呢
I once met a girl who didn't like juggling.
她现在依旧不喜欢
And she still doesn't.
所以你们不会再见面了吗
So you're not gonna see her again?
还有什么意义啊
What's the point?
我俩永远不会真正谈恋爱
We're never gonna be in a real relationship.
所以你俩只能是肉体关系吗
Right, so you'll only be in a physical one?
没错
Exactly.
我干嘛和那种人耗费时间
Why would I want to spend time with someone like that?
那种只对滚床单有兴趣的人吗
Someone who is just interested in sex?
没错
Yeah.
-拉杰  你好好...  -等一下
- Raj, do you real... ?- Whoa, hold on.
给他一点时间  他会想通的
Give him a chance. He's gonna get this.
我觉得他不会
I don't think he is.
有什么可想的
What is there to get?
她不想和人坠入爱河
She doesn't want to fall in love.
这样的话
At that point,
我们就只是两个单身人士
all we are is two single people
互相觉得对方有魅力  也喜欢做...
who find each other attractive and enjoy having--
我得走了
Oh, got to go!
你和如琪昨晚如何
So how was your night with Ruchi?
很好
Oh, great.
我们点了外卖  滚了床单  然后拍屁股走人
We ordered in some food, we had sex, I left.
我甚至不用问她爽不爽
I didn't even ask if she enjoyed it.
这道题我可以替她回答了
I can field that one for her.
我道别时的确有点小哽咽
I mean, I did get a little misty when we said good-bye,
不过我假装自己过敏了
but I played it off as allergies.
不知道她相信没
I don't know if she bought it.
再一次  我知道答案
Again, I know.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
你还好吧
You okay?
谢尔顿
Sheldon.